(Raj:)and pulled and pulled.
(Leonard:)You do what you want,
(Leonard:)I'm not touching another
man's honey tree.
(Raj:)All right, uh,
forget pulling.
(Raj:)How about we get
an electric saw and cut it off?
What?! No saws!
(Howard:)One circumcision was enough.
(Leonard:)How about an
acetylene torch?
(Howard:)Okay, I can't believe
this needs to be said out loud.
(Howard:)No pulling, no saws, no torches.
(Leonard:)Well, then what do
you want us to do?
MRS. WOLOWITZ
Howard, I made cookies for you
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)and your little friends!
(Howard:)That's great, Mom, thanks!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I'll bring them up
with some Hawaiian Punch!
(Howard:)Don't come up here!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Why not?! Are you
ashamed of your mother?!
(Howard:)Yes, but that's not the point!
(Howard:)Get me out of here.
(Leonard:)You have any ideas, Raj?
(Raj:)Right now, all I can think about
is cookies and Hawaiian Punch.